{
    "data": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "category": "Numbers",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "1",
                        "front": "一"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "2",
                        "front": "二"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "3",
                        "front": "三"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "4",
                        "front": "四"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "5",
                        "front": "五"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "6",
                        "front": "六"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "7",
                        "front": "七"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "8",
                        "front": "八"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "9",
                        "front": "九"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "10",
                        "front": "十"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 11,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "11",
                        "front": "十一"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 12,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "12",
                        "front": "十二"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 13,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "13",
                        "front": "十三"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 14,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "14",
                        "front": "十四"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 15,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "15",
                        "front": "十五"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 16,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "16",
                        "front": "十六"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 17,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "17",
                        "front": "十七"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 18,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "18",
                        "front": "十八"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 19,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "19",
                        "front": "十九"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 20,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "20",
                        "front": "二十"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "category": "Colors",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Red",
                        "front": "赤"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Blue",
                        "front": "青"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Green",
                        "front": "緑"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Orange",
                        "front": "オレンジ"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Purple",
                        "front": "紫"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Yellow",
                        "front": "黄色"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Black",
                        "front": "黒"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "White",
                        "front": "白"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Brown",
                        "front": "茶色"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Pink",
                        "front": "ピンク"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "category": "Verbs",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to eat",
                        "front": "食べる"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to drink",
                        "front": "飲む"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to sleep",
                        "front": "寝る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to get up",
                        "front": "起きる"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to read",
                        "front": "読む"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to wear",
                        "front": "着る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to laugh",
                        "front": "笑う"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to dance",
                        "front": "踊る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to run",
                        "front": "走る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to walk",
                        "front": "歩く"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 11,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to open",
                        "front": "開ける"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 12,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to sit",
                        "front": "座る"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 13,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "to write",
                        "front": "書く"
                    }
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "category": "Adjectives",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Big",
                        "front": "大きい"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Small",
                        "front": "小さい"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Slow",
                        "front": "遅い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Fast",
                        "front": "速い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Near",
                        "front": "近く"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Far",
                        "front": "遠い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Good",
                        "front": "良い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Bad",
                        "front": "悪い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 9,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Many",
                        "front": "多い"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "id": 10,
                    "text": {
                        "back": "Few",
                        "front": "少し"
                    }
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}